{
    "id": "555b3c6598d9491596e268d9f6f758e1",
    "title": "Two Word Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The politician broke ———————– in the middle of his speech.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "up",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dfad4375631445a198c259aec2188d1c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you blow —————– the candle?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b9fa41d0b894df69e09b9b889fed3b4"
        },
        {
            "question": "At last the storm has blown —————-",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "over",
                "off",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "61aaa7ccc22a448f9e82c7acb1e50217"
        },
        {
            "question": "The opposition parties said that they would bring ————– a No-Confidence Motion against the Prime Minister.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "forward",
                "out",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e9ed045e840b4c05837c7b5fb237af76"
        },
        {
            "question": "The witness said that she could not call ————— the whole events.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4ae94f7e1944eb4a4e9ce7c282efc02"
        },
        {
            "question": "The labour union leaders have called —————- the strike.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "off",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a1d9c15b40ed45a09ade1649591ed047"
        },
        {
            "question": "The investigating officer tried to call —————- vital information from the accused.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "forth",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd73abe7e4cc48d2873e2cfa061709ea"
        },
        {
            "question": "The army foiled the terrorists’ plan to blow ——————— the bridge.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7788f666f8c242c383cb3c48b49ead35"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is cut —————- for a career in sales and marketing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d46b85c5c8b84cd9ba44dc342b1b103e"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you work hard, you will come ——————- with flying colors in the examination.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "403b0b83a87f4841ab7aa2f07bdd6bc1"
        }
    ]
}